### ROMARIC DEMBELE

### INTERNSHIP IN SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

#### CONTACT -

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

**EMAIL:** 

romadembele@gmail.com

**PHONE:** 

033-074-971-5318

**ADDRESS:** 

Saint-Nazaire, 44600

Adaptable Computer Science major currently attending CESI Engineering school, with 3 months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of programming and application development skills to successfully fill the Internship in Software developer role at your company. Frequently praised as focused by my peers, can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

#### **EDUCATION**

## CESI ENGINEERING SCHOOL FRANCE / Saint-Nazaire

IT-computer science Engineering Computer Science Candidate (Expected graduation Sep 2024)

# CPGE LASALLE BURKINA FASO / Ouagadougou

Mathematics Physics and Engineering science (Jul 2020)

### Science (un 2020)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Software modeling - UML, MCD Web development - ASP .Net Core MVC, Entity Framework, SQL SERVER Project Management, Version

control using Git Test Automation – Robot Framework, Selenium Library

#### CERTIFICATIONS

CISCO CCNA 1 Introduction to Networks Learn C# Codecademy

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## QA Test Automation Engineer Apprentice SharingCloud, FRANCE / Nantes Dec 2021 - Present

API tests implementation Web tests implementation Working in collaboration with the other developer squads

#### **Website Project**

#### CESI Engineering School Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

This project consisted of setting up a responsive website in the form of a PWA respecting the MVC architecture and representing an internship search platform.

### Networks and Systems Project CESI Engineering School Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

In a group of four people, coordination and participation in the configuration (including securing) of the equipment of a Cisco Packet Tracer network model representing a connected city.

## Object Oriented Programming Project CESI Engineering School Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

With two other classmates, a management application (client-server type) was coded in C++.

## Embedded System Project CESI Engineering School Oct 2020 - Oct 2020

This project was made in collaboration with four classmates as part of the problem-based learning (PBL) offered by CESI. The project involved building a radio station prototype using an Arduino board and the Arduino C programming language.